timhortons.com 2006-06-20

# timhortons

Tim Hortons respects the privacy of visitors to our website. To that end, we have developed this Website Privacy Policy to educate visitors to our website about the collection of information by Tim Hortons as a result of the services available on our website. Our Privacy Policy is based on the principles outlined in Canada's Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act, and applicable provincial legislation. If you do not agree to the terms outlined in this Privacy Policy, we ask that you notify us in writing about your concerns ([click here](mailto:privacy@timhortons.com) to send us an e-mail). Alternatively, you have the option of not continuing to visit our site.

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

While visiting the Tim Hortons web site you may be invited to provide us with personal information. The type of information that we collect will depend on the services that you use on our website. Below is a summary of the personal information that we collect, including the purposes for which it is collected:

Customer Questions, Comments or Suggestions: Our website enables you to provide us your questions, comments or suggestions about our products or services. If you send us such a comment and ask us to respond, then we will collect your name, address and telephone number so that we may address your comment and provide you with a timely response.

Résumés: Our website also enables you to apply online for a job with Tim Hortons. If you submit your résumé, then we will collect the information contained in it for the sole purpose of determining your suitability for the position for which you applied.

Surveys: We occasionally post surveys on our website and the information derived from these surveys helps us to improve our service to our customers. Your participation in any such survey is strictly voluntary.

Tim Hortons Scholarship Program: When a Tim Hortons employee (or his or her children or grandchildren) apply for a scholarship, we collect certain personal information (as outlined in the online application form) in order to determine the applicant's eligibility for a scholarship. Any personal information that you provide to Tim Hortons in relation to the scholarship program will be used solely for (1) the administration of the scholarship program and (2) media releases and other public relations materials in relation to the promotion of the scholarship program.

Use of Your Personal Information: We only use your personal information for the purposes stated above, and we do not sell or disclose your personal information without your consent.

Disclosure of Personal Information: Canadian law dictates that we may disclose personal information without consent for law enforcement and national security purposes, for debt collection, to a lawyer representing our organization, and in an emergency situation in which an individual's life, health or security is threatened.

## Use of Cookies

The Tim Hortons web site uses cookies to track general user trends and patterns. A cookie is a small piece of information that a web site stores on your computer. It is retrieved automatically whenever you return and some of its contents are stored in log files that are then used to generate periodic statistical reports. These reports help us to evaluate and improve our web sites by tracking global indicators such as the total number of visitors, total pages viewed, most popular documents retrieved, etc.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to alert you when one is being sent. However, some parts of the Tim Hortons web site, and affiliated web sites, may not work properly if you choose not to accept cookies. For additional information on cookies, see the Help instructions on your browser.

## Confidentiality

Throughout the site, visitors are given an opportunity to provide us with feedback. When you provide us with feedback, we will not share your name with others. We will only use the information provided by you in order to respond to your feedback.

We will amend our records and, where appropriate, advise third parties regarding any changes to ensure the accuracy and completeness of your personal information.

## Subject to Change

This privacy policy is subject to change at any time.

## Contact Information

If you wish to request access to information, or have any question about the Tim Hortons Privacy Policy, or wish to receive a full copy of the Tim Horton's Customer Privacy Policy and Procedures, please contact Mr. Steven Kahansky who is the Chief Privacy Officer for Tim Hortons' head office and its affiliates. Mr. Kahansky can be reached at [privacy@timhortons.com](mailto:privacy@timhortons.com).
